&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们跳到this关键字，然后
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's jump into the this keyword, and
尝试通过代码更好地理解它。
try to understand it a little bit better through code.
让我们在这个练习中编写一些代码。
Let's write some code in this exercise.
在本练习中，您将重构一些当前使用的代码
In this exercise you're gonna be refactoring some code that currently uses
模块模式，您将改为使其使用名称空间模式
the module pattern, and you're gonna instead make it use that namespace pattern
在对象上有方法的地方，并且
where you have methods on an object and
它们使用this关键字引用该对象的数据属性。
they refer to the data properties on that object using the this keyword.
因此，如果我们查看ex.js，您会注意到我们有我们的模块定义。
So if we look at the ex.js you'll notice that we have our module definition.
我们已经得到了这个定义的工作坊()函数，它是我们的工厂函数。
We've got this defineWorkshop() function, which is our factory function.
它产生了这个public API对象，它有这些内部的东西，
It's producing this publicAPI object and it has these internal things,
这些内部数据值，如currentEnrollment和StudentRecords。
these internal data values, like currentEnrollment and studentRecords.
我们想要做的是把深度JS从函数定义变成
What we wanna do is turn the deepJS from being defined by a function to
被定义为具有
being defined as an object literal that has
引用currentEnrollment和StudentRecords的属性。
properties that reference the currentEnrollment and studentRecords.
所有这些功能，而不是隐藏，它们都将是公开的
And all of those functions, instead of being hidden, they'll all be public
方法，它们都会用这个stop进行引用。
methods on that object and they'll all make references with this stop.
提醒一句，这段代码中有很多地方。
A word of caution, that there are a bunch of places within this code.
例如，我们在这里传递一个像这样的回调。
For example, we pass in a callback like this one right here.
我们将此回调传递给.map。
We pass in this callback to .map.
当它是一个常规的词汇功能时，
When it’s a regular lexical function,
它在模块模式中的方式，没有任何问题。
the way it is in the module pattern, no problem whatsoever.
但是当我们将这个传递给Where函数时，
But when we pass in this to where functions,
我们有我们这个装订的问题。
we have the problem of our this binding.
所以你需要确保注意你需要的地方
So you need to make sure to watch out for the places where you need
来传递对方法的硬绑定引用，好吗？
to pass in hard-bound references to the methods, okay?
所以自述文件会给你关于取出的说明
So the readme will give you the instructions on taking out
定义工作坊()工厂，用一个对象替换它。
the defineWorkshop() factory, replacing it with an object.
更改所有这些内部基准电压源和
Change all those internal references and
确保在需要的地方使用绑定，但不要使用绑定
make sure that you use the bind where it's needed, but don't use the bind on
因为并不是所有的函数调用都需要它。
everything because it's not needed for all of the function calls.
一如既往，如果你遇到困难需要帮助，
As always, if you get stuck and need some help,
确保查看解决方案文件ex.Fixed。
make sure to look at the solution file, the ex.fixed.
我们几分钟后回来讨论解决方案。
We'll be back in a few minutes to talk through the solution.